https://www.cholley.com/privacy-policy/

Swiss SkincareProductsAnti-Aging & LiftingSkin WhiteningEye ContourAnti-AcneSkin RepairDetox & Anti-StressToners and CleansersPeelingProfessional MasksSun ProtectionSlimming and Anti-CelluliteBody Firming and Stretch MarksCollectionsCHOLLEY Phytocell®Super Premium Anti-Aging Products with IC-RAMP® Technology & Swiss Phyto Stem CellsCHOLLEY PHYTOBIOTECH SYSTEM®Super Premium Product for Damaged, Dull & Stressed Skins with New Generation of Swiss BiotechnologyCHOLLEY®Anti-Aging & Whitening Program based on the Best of Swiss Phytobiology for all Skin typesBIOCLEAN®Specific Program for Oily, Acne & Impure SkinsBIOREGENE®Intense Hydration & Regeneration Program for Dry. Very Dry & Delicate SkinsCELLIPEX®Best-known Slimming & Anti-Cellulite Program in Switzerland for Body Draining & ReshapingBIOLASTON®Specially developed to Tone, Nourish, Moisturize & Prevent Stretch MarksBIOFORCE®Premium Products specially formulated to Purify, Soothe, Hydrate the Male SkinTreatmentsTechnologyIC-RAMP® TechnologySwiss Stem CellsNews & BlogWhat’s newBLOGNewsletterPressVideo Product Function &#038; UseAbout UsSwiss LaboratoriesContact usBecome our partnerHomeCustomer Privacy Policy in our SiteCustomer Privacy Policy in our SiteProtecting your privacy is important to CHOLLEY SA. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the CHOLLEY SA Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.Why we collect personal information CHOLLEY SA collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, special offers, and other information we think you’d like to hear about. This may occasionally include information about products and services that can add value to your CHOLLEY products. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products.How we collect personal information We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, register to attend a seminar, or participate in an online survey. In addition, when you register a new CHOLLEY product, sign up for CHOLLEY SA Internet services, or ask to be included in an email mailing list, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.To save you time and make our web services even easier to use, some areas of the CHOLLEY SA website allow you to create an “CHOLLEY ID” using your personal information. Here’s how it works: Simply fill out a brief profile—your name, phone number, and email address—then choose a password and password hint (such as the month and day of your birth) for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal CHOLLEY ID. Next time you order something from the CHOLLEY Store or register a new product, you can simply enter your email address and password—the system will automatically look up the information it needs.When we disclose personal information Because CHOLLEY SA is a global company, your personal information may be shared with other CHOLLEY SA business units around the world. They will protect your personal information in accordance with the CHOLLEY SA Customer Privacy Policy. CHOLLEY may occasionally share your personal contact information with carefully selected technology companies, to keep you informed about related products and services. At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.How we protect your personal information CHOLLEY SA safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.Collecting other personal information When you browse CHOLLEY SA’s website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don’t collect personal information when you browse — not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.Like many websites, the CHOLLEY SA website uses “cookie” technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you, except perhaps your first name so we can welcome you on your next visit. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.CHOLLEY SA does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.CHOLLEY SA’s website contains links to other sites. CHOLLEY SA does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.The CHOLLEY SA Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.FOLLOW US |
|
|
|Sitemap
COLLECTIONSCHOLLEY PHYTOCELL®CHOLLEY PHYTOBIOTECH®CHOLLEY®BIOCLEAN®BIOREGENE®CELLIPEX® ABOUT US CONTACT USBEST SELLERSSwiss Anti-Aging Creams & SerumsSkin Repair CreamsSkin Brightening Serum CreamBest Eye Creams for Dark Circles and PuffinessBest Anti-Acne Skincare SolutionsPeeling face MasksProfessional MasksSun Protection CreamNEWSCHOLLEY’s 30 Years Anniversary Gala Night – 11 October 2019CHOLLEY’S 30th Anniversary Celebration with Maison-Dellos in MoscowCHOLLEY Press Conference in MoscowBeauty Trade Special 2019 with 247 Cosmetics in UtrechtCHOLLEY @ The WORLD ECONOMY FORUM 2019 in Davos
Swiss SkincareProductsAnti-Aging & LiftingSkin WhiteningEye ContourAnti-AcneSkin RepairDetox & Anti-StressToners and CleansersPeelingProfessional MasksSun ProtectionSlimming and Anti-CelluliteBody Firming and Stretch MarksCollectionsCHOLLEY Phytocell®Super Premium Anti-Aging Products with IC-RAMP® Technology & Swiss Phyto Stem CellsCHOLLEY PHYTOBIOTECH SYSTEM®Super Premium Product for Damaged, Dull & Stressed Skins with New Generation of Swiss BiotechnologyCHOLLEY®Anti-Aging & Whitening Program based on the Best of Swiss Phytobiology for all Skin typesBIOCLEAN®Specific Program for Oily, Acne & Impure SkinsBIOREGENE®Intense Hydration & Regeneration Program for Dry. Very Dry & Delicate SkinsCELLIPEX®Best-known Slimming & Anti-Cellulite Program in Switzerland for Body Draining & ReshapingBIOLASTON®Specially developed to Tone, Nourish, Moisturize & Prevent Stretch MarksBIOFORCE®Premium Products specially formulated to Purify, Soothe, Hydrate the Male SkinTreatmentsTechnologyIC-RAMP® TechnologySwiss Stem CellsNews & BlogWhat’s newBLOGNewsletterPressVideo Product Function &#038; UseAbout UsSwiss LaboratoriesContact usBecome our partner
